NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
Burn
Byakugan!
This Is My Way of the Ninja
Kiba!
Naruto!
This isn't good.
Oh my, what's wrong?
So you'll just stay there
and become larvae food?
Queen Bee...
That kind of stuff shouldn't
be effective should it?!
Chakra...!
Byakugan!
It's no good... There's no way
I can make it in time!
Naruto...
I don't know when to give up!
That's right...
I know that Naruto would never give up
no matter what the situation is!
Hey, did you catch them?
What a foolish group!
They made this creature mad...
And they all got bound in wax!
Bees make wax.
You're an insect handler
and you don't know that?
He's right!
C'mon are you really an insect handler?
What about the Bikochu?
Nothing.
We did an all-out mobilization
and searched
but we haven't found it.
Aren't these guys carrying it?
That's unthinkable.
So that means...
So we're going to have to
ask one of these guys after all.
Who's gonna talk?!
We can tell you.
Shino!
However...
It's in exchange for Hinata.
That's stupid isn't it? To bargain...
Do you not understand your position?
You guys definitely will not
find the Bikochu.
And you're pressed for time.
You are the ones... who will regret it.
What should we do?
If things stay like this
the Bikochu won't be of any help
even if it hatches.
In that case our mission is also...
But...
If we can get rid of even one
of the Aburame family...
Hinata...
Are you worried?
Of course!
She's strong.
Huh?
Much more... than you think.
I concede. We have a deal.
First of all, we need our friend.
What happened?
The brat... isn't here.
The wax she was trapped in isn't there....
She may have been swept out
to the waterfall.
Jibachi!
It can't be helped! I warned her not
to make a bad move or she'd die.
You!
What did you do to Hinata?!
What happened to Hinata! Hey!
Shut up kid.
The kid's probably in
the depths of hell about now.
Damn you!
Aha, the girl's your girlfriend?
You...! I absolutely will not forgive you!
You're kidding me.
What can you do looking like that?
Without Hinata you'll never get
your hands on the Bikochu either.
You are right...
That girl's death was not part
of the plan
but in the end it's a good thing.
Because... we'll take your lives in return.
From the very beginning people from
the Village Hidden in the Leaves and
from my own Village Hidden in the Stones
have been sworn enemies.
It's natural that we kill
each other, isn't it?
What're ya gonna do, little guy?
Die like this?
Or if you tell me where the Bikochu is
I could save you for now.
— All right.
— Don't you dare tell them!
Those jerks,
I'm going to blow them away!
Shut up brat!
— Jibachi?
— Hey!
Shut up, I've got to kill him!
It's a Paper Bomb!
You're...!
Y-You're...!
...still alive!
That was really close.
But I didn't give up just like Naruto...
Did she escape from the wax?
It can't be!
These are not ordinary kids.
Leave it to me!
Hinata!
I've never used that in an actual fight...
But I have to do it here now!
Bee Bombs Jutsu!
1000 Bee Stingers Jutsu!
Bee Swarm Jutsu!
Naruto...
Naruto... Watch me.
Protective 8 Trigrams 64 palms!
— What?!
You're kidding, right?
That Hinata can do
such an amazing Jutsu?
The Hinata that you know Naruto
is from when?
What do you mean?
You've learned new Jutsu
since the Chunin Ninja Exam, haven't you?
Hinata has been steadily developing too.
She always has been concerned...
Take aim.
That's nice the three of you
all have something you're good at
and something you like.
Hinata, you should find something too...
You're right.
By the way what is it?
You had some business with me,
didn't you?
Yeah...
I want you to join me
in my training.
Hinata was fretting over
what she could do...
What she should do...
Hinata!
Hey, I don't think that we should...
No... Don't go easy on me!
If you're doing it for me...
Do it seriously!
I've got it!
During the harsh training
Hinata discovered her own styles...
and her own special Jutsu.
That's the result of her training.
Huh? You why!?
I'll tell you something...
Angering the Queen Bee
getting encased in wax
it was all part of the strategy.
With our Chakra being sucked
and being immobilized
it was the only way to protect ourselves
from the larvae...
And do you think I was doing nothing
while I was captured?
I was ordering my bugs.
The wax we're wrapped in is very weak.
Shino!
Because of her hard training
Hinata's Chakra control
has dramatically improved.
That Jutsu is what she developed
from the training...
Protective 8 trigrams 64 palms!
Hinata's already flexible body combined
with fine-tuned Chakra control
could completely defend
an attack from every direction...
Truly it's an ultimate defense Jutsu.
Yet it's different from
Neji's 8 Trigrams Palms Rotation.
It's Hinata's own Jutsu...
She finally worked that out on her own.
She probably did it because she wanted
to be acknowledged by her father.
To be acknowledged by everyone...
And to be acknowledged by you.
Our Jutsu isn't effective at all?!
What the hell is going on?
What a girl!
Hey, what happened to those guys?!
When did they?!
Summoning Jutsu!
Blow them away!
Hinata!
Shino!
Believe... in her.
Make the Chakra...
sharper, stronger...
bigger, more flexible...
more... more... more...
more... more... more... more!
Hinata!
Naruto...
Hinata, that's an awesome Jutsu!
You're really awesome!
Naruto...!
Let's hurry. It'll be dawn soon.
— Okay!
— Yeah!
Oh, it's becoming a pupa already?
If we make it smell Sasuke's scent
at the moment it hatches
the mission is complete.
Right!
Sasuke... Wait for me!
No way!
Inside the tree, huh.
If it was there
the bees should have found it...
You can still move?
This insect cage was coated
with secret Aburame family insect repellent.
Wh-What?
The bees won't come close
because of the repellent.
As long as you're using bees to search...
you definitely won't find it.
I expected as much.
I think as long as your clan exists...
my clan maybe destined to
be ruined some day.
But!
I absolutely will not let you
succeed at your mission!
Even if it kills me, that Bikochu...
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
This is our hope...
in order to get our friend back!
I won't let you do that!
Shut up!
Rasengan!
Hey look...
The pupa is hatching!
Okay!
Huh? It's gone!
You had it 'til just a minute ago!
Hey, search for it hurry!
R-Right...
Byakugan!
Naruto! Over there.
You blew it away the instant you set off
the Rasengan!
Hurry!
I know!
C'mon, c'mon.
It's going to hatch!
We did it! Hurry make it sniff this...
Wh-Why...?!
That thing just now doesn't count!
C'mon sniff Sasuke's smell!
— It's all over now.
— Huh...?
Hey! Stop! Wait!
So you failed because you farted!
Take responsibility!
What are you saying that for?!
Well then...
That's... the Bikochu isn't it?
Naruto... I found you!
C'mon forgive me already, Sakura!
No! I absolutely will not forgive you!
— Sakura, you look so scary!
— Come back here!
So the mission failed...
It seems that they succeeded
at protecting the Bikochu
but failed at getting it to smell
the scent of Uchiha Sasuke.
I see... Hinata must be depressed.
This strategy was her idea, wasn't it?
Well... Looks like that's not the case.
Hinata... I heard that your mission failed.
Yes. It didn't work at all.
I have to train more and more...
and work harder next time!
I-I see... Good luck.
More...
More!
kusottare na nyuusu ga toori sugite
crappy news pass us by
kimi wa kotoba wo nakusu
and you become speechless
boku no koe ja marude chiisa sugite
my voice is way too soft
kimi wa henji mo shinai
so you don't answer
kimi ga naiteru hitori de naiteru
you're crying, crying alone
boku wa dou suru boku mo naiteru no sa
what can I do? I'm crying too
yoru ni hitoribocchi no ore no sakebi ni nosete
"let my lonely scream ring out through the night"
zawameku jidai wo ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll thrash this confused era with my speed, yeah
sanzameku yoru mo ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
and I'll thrash this confused night with my speed, yeah
tsunzaku gitaa to ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar and my speed, yeah
katamuku sekai mo warui yatsura mo kechirashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll take this sinking world, all its evil bastards, and kick their butts, yeah
What! Why do I have to go on
such an easy mission?!
Don't complain! You're the one
who picked up this mission's client!
That's no reason!
After all I'm busy with a lot stuff!
That's enough
or I'll send you back to the Academy!
That's not fair...
No arguments!
Neji, Tenten, Lee, Naruto!
The four of you,
I'm delivering your new mission.
Next episode:
"A Funeral March For the Living."